<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" standalone = "no" ?>
<news>
    <EN>
        <title>Last generation technologies</title>
        <text1>We believe that success in diagnosing and treating general and especially dental conditions depends on
            how
            quickly the condition is identified and the accuracy of the results. We work daily to eliminate lost time,
            energy and resources, to make sure our treatments are better, faster and less expensive for our patients.
        </text1>
        <text2>We use digital technologies that give the patient the opportunity to view the final treatment even before
            starting it. Thus, it becomes an active part of the treatment process, the doctor taking into account all
            aspects - medical, aesthetic, emotional, which it entails.
        </text2>
        <text3>We use the most powerful intraoral scanner in the world, 3Shape Trios, through which we manage to restore
            digital comfort to patients. Half the time you sat with your mouth open is gone. Everything happens in a
            digital
            clone of your mouth, and then it is transferred with an accuracy of 20 microns intra-orally.
        </text3>
    </EN>
    <RO>
        <title>Tehnologii performante de ultima generație</title>
        <text1>Credem că succesul în diagnosticarea și tratamentul afecțiunilor generale și, în special, stomatologice,
            depinde de rapiditatea cu care este identificată afecțiunea și precizia rezultatelor. Lucrăm zilnic pentru a
            elimina timpul, energia și resursele pierdute, pentru a ne asigura că tratamentele noastre sunt mai bune,
            mai rapide și mai puțin costisitoare pentru pacienții noștri.
        </text1>
        <text2>Folosim tehnologiile digitale care oferă pacientului posibilitatea de a vizualiza tratamentul final încă
            dinainte de a-l începe. Astfel, acesta devine parte activă a procesului de elaborare a tratamentului,
            doctorul ținând seama de toate aspectele – medicale, estetice, emoționale, pe care acesta le presupune.
        </text2>
        <text3>Utilizăm cel mai performant scanner intraoral din lume, 3Shape Trios prin intermediul căruia reușim să
            redăm pacienților confortul digital. Jumătate din timpul în care stăteai cu gura deschisă acum a dispărut.
            Totul se întâmplă într-o clonă digitală a gurii tale, iar apoi e transferat cu o precizie de 20 microni
            intra-oral.
        </text3>
    </RO>
</news>